{"sid": "CG4PXZDQNRHF_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 424616, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 424619, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 441399]], "time_left_end": "284", "answered_time": 441399, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "284", "question_time_start": 441400, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 453804]], "time_left_end": "271", "answered_time": 453804, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "271", "question_time_start": 453805, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 458519]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 458519, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 458519, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 469190]], "time_left_end": "256", "answered_time": 469190, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "False", "score": "2"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "256", "question_time_start": 469190, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 473685]], "time_left_end": "251", "answered_time": 473685, "user_answer": "23", "user_correct": "False", "score": "1"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "251", "question_time_start": 473686, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["calc_1", 479222], ["calc_6", 479863], ["calc_+", 480428], ["calc_7", 481280], ["calc_8", 481909], ["calc_6", 482561], ["calc_=", 483243], ["submit", 492401]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "233", "answered_time": 492401, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "233", "question_time_start": 492402, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 501112]], "time_left_end": "224", "answered_time": 501112, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "224", "question_time_start": 501112, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 511351]], "time_left_end": "214", "answered_time": 511351, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "214", "question_time_start": 511351, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 518940]], "time_left_end": "206", "answered_time": 518940, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "206", "question_time_start": 518942, "question": "7+6+46", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 526219]], "time_left_end": "199", "answered_time": 526219, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 526219, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "199", "question_time_start": 526219, "question": "6+47+16", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 534299]], "time_left_end": "191", "answered_time": 534299, "user_answer": "69", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "191", "question_time_start": 534300, "question": "19+499", "correct_answer": 518, "events": [["submit", 548528]], "time_left_end": "177", "answered_time": 548528, "user_answer": "518", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "177", "question_time_start": 548528, "question": "7+3+6+79", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 555730]], "time_left_end": "169", "answered_time": 555730, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "169", "question_time_start": 555730, "question": "18+57", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 563962]], "time_left_end": "161", "answered_time": 563962, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "161", "question_time_start": 563963, "question": "4+9+9+48", "correct_answer": 70, "events": [["submit", 574902]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 574902, "user_answer": "70", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 574902, "question": "53+56", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 583496]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 583496, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 583496, "question": "8+9+77", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 594933]], "time_left_end": "130", "answered_time": 594933, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "130", "question_time_start": 594933, "question": "7+3+8+38", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 603542]], "time_left_end": "122", "answered_time": 603542, "user_answer": "56", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "122", "question_time_start": 603543, "question": "7+54+64", "correct_answer": 125, "events": [["submit", 621123]], "time_left_end": "104", "answered_time": 621123, "user_answer": "125", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "104", "question_time_start": 621124, "question": "8+4+27", "correct_answer": 39, "events": [["submit", 626539]], "time_left_end": "99", "answered_time": 626539, "user_answer": "39", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 626540, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "99", "question_time_start": 626540, "question": "7+4+8+43", "correct_answer": 62, "events": [["submit", 636092]], "time_left_end": "89", "answered_time": 636092, "user_answer": "62", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "89", "question_time_start": 636093, "question": "7+3+4+58", "correct_answer": 72, "events": [["submit", 641756]], "time_left_end": "83", "answered_time": 641756, "user_answer": "72", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "83", "question_time_start": 641756, "question": "6+6+47", "correct_answer": 59, "events": [["submit", 646374]], "time_left_end": "79", "answered_time": 646374, "user_answer": "59", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "79", "question_time_start": 646376, "question": "4+46+64", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 654091]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 654091, "user_answer": "114", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 654092, "question": "84+383", "correct_answer": 467, "events": [["submit", 667694]], "time_left_end": "57", "answered_time": 667694, "user_answer": "467", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "57", "question_time_start": 667695, "question": "88+44", "correct_answer": 132, "events": [["submit", 680148]], "time_left_end": "45", "answered_time": 680148, "user_answer": "132", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "45", "question_time_start": 680149, "question": "8+7+7+46", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 695336]], "time_left_end": "30", "answered_time": 695335, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "30", "question_time_start": 695336, "question": "13+56", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 702112]], "time_left_end": "23", "answered_time": 702111, "user_answer": "69", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "23", "question_time_start": 702113, "question": "4+23+64", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 709669]], "time_left_end": "15", "answered_time": 709669, "user_answer": "93", "user_correct": "False", "score": "23"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "15", "question_time_start": 709672, "question": "3+9+33", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 718335]], "time_left_end": "7", "answered_time": 718335, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 718336, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "7", "question_time_start": 718336, "question": "46+89", "correct_answer": 135, "events": []}}}}}